

■ jeremyjtlo92@gmail.com | • jeremy-jtlo | • jeremy-lo-7131017b

Summary _

Currently, I'm a React developer at Microsoft Canada, but my previous experience includes Electronic Arts and BlackBerry. I am driven to solve problems by improving code maintainability, eliminating tech debt, and ensuring everyone on a team can grow. My ideal work environment is one where I can challenge myself to constantly improve.

So if you need something built, I build things.

Work Experience

Microsoft Vancouver, Canada

SOFTWARE ENGINEER II May 2021 - PRESENT

- Delivered a new chat experience for Microsoft Teams Rooms (MTR) for Teams 2.1
- · Conduct code reviews and suggest improvements to reduce redundancy and improve test coverage
- · Drive feature development across various timezones by coordinating with designers, testers, and project managers
- Lead refactor effort in an egregious part of legacy UI for mounting MTR view panels
- Create and maintain Jest and Cypress tests to mitigate regressions before submission
- Contributed to existing and new documentation for feature development, migrations, and process changes for newer team members

Electronic Arts CanadaBurnaby, Canada

 Web Developer
 Sep. 2017 - Mar. 2021

- Lead integration of brand-new 'vanity' items to FUT Companion App users in FIFA20, including nightly asset builds
- Planned, scoped, and implemented new features for current and future releases of the FIFA Ultimate Team Companion apps (FUT19 FUT21)
- Managed Live Content responsibilities such as coordinating roll-outs of exclusive timed campaigns for FUT Companions
- Refactored legacy tools for parsing app metadata to reduce development overhead on CI pipeline
- Prevented content leaks, cut build times by exposing and resolving issues in 2D asset pipeline
- Interfaced with producers, developers, and testers across Live Content, Server, and Console teams in Canada and Romania

Electronic Arts Canada Burnaby, Canada

ASSOCIATE TECHNICAL ARTIST

Jun. 2016 - Sep. 2017

- Wrote and supported existing Maya plugins and other packages used by artists on Rigging team, in C# and Python.
- Collected, assessed, and prioritized feedback on plugins from users.
- Fixed visual bugs on assets and animations using node- and timeline-based editors in proprietary Frostbite engine.

Tantalus Systems

Burnaby, Canada

TEST AUTOMATION ENGINEER (CO-OP)

Jan. 2014 - Aug. 2014

- $\bullet \ \ \text{Reduced setup time in regression testing of server features by automating triage work nightly}$
- · Created tooling with Python lxml and etree to send build e-mail notifications for high impact tickets
- Met daily with teammates to sync progress and design future plans for automation
- Managed Ubuntu and OEL VMs used as build machines and test environments

BlackBerry Canada Waterloo, Canada

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (CO-OP)

Jan. 2013 - Aug. 2013

- $\bullet \ \ \text{Oversaw deployment and automated testing of BES10 servers through Jenkins, Maven, Ant, and VMW are vSphere.}$
- · Created, deployed, and re-tooled scripts used for production and maintenance of build config files.
- Managed instances of test host machines using Windows Server and Ubuntu LTS VMs
- · Investigated and validated new third-party plugins for Hudson/Jenkins before deploying to Continuous Integration Team's production server

Education

Simon Fraser University Burnaby, Canada

B.Sc. IN COMPUTING SCIENCE

Sep. 2010 - May. 2016

• Graduated with a Minor in Interactive Art and Technology

AUGUST 5, 2024 JEREMY LO · RÉSUMÉ 1